Finding Aid for the United States Ephemera Collection LSC.0609
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Grand Teton National Park. (Box 22)
- Grannan, Riley. (Box 23)
- Grant, Frederick Dent, 1850-1912. (Box 23)
- Grants Pass, Oregon. (Box 23)
- Graves, John Temple, 1856-1925. (Box 23)
- Gray, Asa, 1810-1888. (Box 23)
- Great Salt Lake. (Box 23)
- Greble, John Trout, 1834-1861. (Box 23)
- Greeley, Horace, 1811-1872. (Box 23)
- Greely, Adolphus Washington, 1844-1935. (Box 23)
- Green, Hetty Howland (Robinson), 1834-1916. (Box 23)
- Greene, Nathanael, 1742-1786. (Box 23)
- Greeting cards. (Box 117)
- Gregg, Josiah, 1806-1850? (Box 23)
- Gregory, Thomas Watt, 1861-1933. (Box 23)
- Gresham, Walter Quintin, 1832-1895. (Box 23)
- Grey, Zane, 1872-1939. (Box 23)
- Gridiron Club (The). Washington, D.C.. (Box 117)
- Grierson, Francis, 1848 -1927. (Box 23)
- Grigg, John, 1792-1864. (Box 23)
- Griggs, Edward Howard, 1868 - (Box 23)
- Gronlund, Laurence, 1846-1899. (Box 23)
- Gross, Charles Philip, 1889. (Box 23)
- Gruber, Frank, 1904 - (Box 23)
- Guggenheim, C.W. (Box 23)
- Guild, Curtis, 1827-1911. (Box 23)
- Guiney, Louise Imogen, 1861-1920. (Box 23)
- Gunsaulus, Frank Wakeley, 1856-1921. (Box 23)
- Hailmann, William Nichols, 1836-1920. (Box Unknown container 230 for instance of Hailmann, William Nichols, 1836-1920.)
- Haldeman-Julius publications. Girard, Kansas. (Box 23)
- Hale, Edward Everett, 1822-1909 (Box 23)
- Hale, Mrs. Sarah Josespha (Buell), 1788-1879. (Box 23)
- Hall, Abraham Oakey, 1826-1898. (Box 23)
- Hall, Bolton, 1854-1938. (Box 23)
- Hall, Granville Stanley, 1844-1924. (Box 114)
- Halleck, Fitz-Greene, 1790-1867. (Box 114)
- Halsey, William Frederick, 1882 - (Box 114)
- Hamilton, Alexander, 1757-1804. (Box 114)
- Hamlin, Hannibal, 1809-1891. (Box 114)
- Hammett, Dashiell, 1894-1961. (Box 24)
- Hanby, Benjamin Russel, 1833-1867. (Box 24)
- Hancock, Winfield Scott, 1824-1886. (Box 24)
- Hardwick, Thomas William, 1872-1944. (Box 24)
- Harlan, James, 1820 -1899. (Box 24)
- Harnett, Cornelius, 1723-1781. (Box 24)
- Harris, William Torrey, 1835-1909. (Box 24)
- Harrison, Charles Custis, 1844-1929. (Box 24)
- Harrison, Leon, 1866-1928. (Box 24)
- Hartmann, Sadakichi, 1867-1944. (Box 24)
- Hartt, Charles Frederic, 1840-1878. (Box 24)
- Harvard University., [4 folders.] (Box 83)
- Haskin, Frederick Jennings, 1872-1944. (Box 24)
- Hastings, Samuel Dexter, 1816-1903. (Box 24)
- Hawaiian Islands., [4 folders.] (Box 115)
- Hawkins, Benjamin, 1754-1816. (Box 24)
- Hawley, Joseph Roswell, 1826-1905. (Box 24)
- Hawthorne, Julian, 1846-1934. (Box 24)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel, 1804-1868. (Box 24)
- Hay, John, 1838-1905. (Box 24)
- Hayne, Paul Hamilton, 1830-1886. (Box 24)
- Hayne, William Hamilton, 1856-1929. (Box 24)
- Haynes, Frank Jay, 1853-1920? (Box 24)
- Hazen, William Babcock, 1830-1887. (Box 24)
- Headley, Joel Tyler, 1813-1897. (Box 24)
- Hearn, Lafcadio, 1850-1904. (Box 24)
- Hecht, Ben, 1893-1964. (Box 25)
- Heifetz, Jascha, 1901 - (Box 25)
- Hellman, Lillian, 1905-1984. (Box 25)
- Hemingway, Ernest, 1899-1961., [2 folders.] (Box 25)
- Hemlock Society. (Box 25)
- Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878. (Box 25)
- Herbs. (Box 25)
- Herron, George Davis, 1862-1925. (Box 25)
- Hersey, John Richard, 1914 - (Box 25)
- Herzog, Herman, 1832-1932. (Box 25)
- Hewitt, Abraham Stevens, 1822-1903. (Box 25)
- Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1823-1911. (Box 25)
- Higinbotham, Harlow Niles, 1838-1919. (Box 25)
- Hilgard, Julius Erasmus, 1825-1891. (Box 25)
- Hill, George William, 1838-1914. (Box 25)
- Hillers, John K. (Box 25)
- Hilles, Charles Dewey, 1867-1949. (Box 25)
- Hillis, Newell Dwight, 1858-1929. (Box 25)
- Hilprecht, Herman Volrath, 1859-1929. (Box 25)
- Hine, Lewis Wickes, 1874-1970. (Box 25)
- Historical Society of New Mexico. (Box 26)
- Hoadley, George, 1826-1902. (Box 26)
- Hobson, Richard Pearson, 1870-1937. (Box 26)
- Hodgson, Richard, 1855-1905. (Box 26)
- Hoe, Richard March, 1812-1886. (Box 26)
- Hoffman, Charles Fenno, 1806-1884. (Box 26)
- Holcomb, Thomas, 1879 - (Box 26)
- Holland, Josiah Gilbert, 1819-1881. (Box 26)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1809-1894. (Box 26)
- Homer, Louise Dilworth (Beatty), 1871 -1947. (Box 26)
- Homer, Winslow, 1836-1910. (Box 26)
- Hoover Dam., [2 folders.] (Box 26)
- Hoover, Herbert. (Box 26)
- Hopeland, Oregon. (Box 26)
- Hopkins, Mark, 1802-1887. (Box 26)
- Hopkinson, Francis, 1737-1791. (Box 26)
- Hopper, DeWolf, 1858-1935. (Box 26)
- Horgan, Paul, 1903 - (Box 26)
- Hornaday, William Temple, 1854-1937. (Box 41)
- Horse racing-U.S. (Box 41)
- Hosmer, Harriet Goodhue, 1830-1908. (Box 41)
- Hotels, taverns, etc.-U.S. (Box 41)
- Houston, David Franklin, 1866-1940. (Box 27)
- Houston, Samuel, 1793-1863. (Box 27)
- Houston, Texas. (Box 27)
- Howard, Oliver Otis, 1830-1909. (Box 27)
- Howe, Henry, 1816 -1893. (Box 27)
- Howe, Julia Ward, 1819-1910. (Box 27)
- Howe, Louis McHenry, 1871-1936. (Box 27)
- Howells, William Dean, 1837-1920. (Box 27)
- Hubbard, Henry, 1784-1857. (Box 27)
- Hughes, Charles Evans, 1862-1948. (Box 27)
- Hughes, Rupert, 1872 - (Box 28)
- Humphrey, Hubert Horatio, 1911 - (Box 28)
- Hungarians in the U.S. (Box 28)
- Hunt, Alice Riggs, 1884 - (Box 28)
- Hunt, William Morris, 1824-1879. (Box 28)
- Huntington, Collis Potter. (Box 117)
- Huntington, Daniel, 1816-1906. (Box 28)
- Husting, Paul Oscar, 1866-1917. (Box 28)
- Hutt, Henry, 1875 - (Box 28)
- Hwange Research Trust. (Box 28)
- Hymns, English. (Box 28)
- Hyslop, James Hervey, 1854-1920. (Box 28)
- I Am., [4 folders.] (Box 84)
- Ickes, Harold Le Claire, 1874-1953. (Box 28)
- Idaho. (Box 28)
- Illinois. (Box 28)
- Inches, Howard Von Hardenburg, 1910 - (Box 28)
- Indiana. (Box 28, Box 127)
- Indians of North America-Arizona. (Box 41)
- Indians of North America-New Mexico. (Box 41)
- Indians of North America-Pacific Coast (North America)-basket making. (Box 41)
- Indians of North America-Southwest, New., [3 folders.] (Box 29)
- Indians of North America., [3 folders.] (Box 28)
- Industry-U.S. (Box 29)
- Ingalls, John James, 1833-1900. (Box 29)
- Ingalls, Melville Ezra, 1842-1914. (Box 29)
- Ingersoll, Charles Jared, 1782-1862. (Box 29)
- Ingersoll, Robert Green, 1833-1899. (Box 29)
- Innes, George, 1825-1894. (Box 29)
- Insurance. (Box 29)
- International Museum of Photography at George Eastman House. (Box 29)
- Inventors, American. (Box 41)
- Iowa. (Box 41)
- Ireland, John 1838-1918. (Box 41)
- Irving, Washington, 1783-1857. (Box 41)
- Jackson, James, 1757-1806. (Box 41)
- Jackson, Thomas Johnathon, 1824- 1863. (Box 41)
- Jackson, William Henry, 1843-1942. (Box 41)
- Jacobi, Abraham, 1830-1919. (Box 41)
- Jacob's Pillow, Mass. (Box 41)
- James, Henry, 1843-1916. (Box 42)
- James, Jesse Woodson, 1847-1882. (Box 30)
- James, Ollie Murray, 1871-1918. (Box 30)
- James, William, 1842-1910. (Box 30)
- Japanese in the U.S. (Box 30)
- Jastrow, Morris, 1861-1921. (Box 30)
- Jay, Mrs. John. (Box 30)
- Jay, William, 1789-1858. (Box 30)
- Jenkins, Charles Francis. (Box 30)
- Jerome, William Travers, 1859-1934. (Box 30)
- Jewett, Sarah Orne, 1849-1909. (Box 30)
- Jews in the U.S., [3 folders.] (Box 30)
- Johnson, Alvin Saunders, 1874 - (Box 31)
- Johnson, J. Seward, 1930 - (Box 31)
- Johnson, Lyndon Baines (family). (Box 31)
- Johnson, Reverdy, 1796-1876. (Box 31)
- Johnson, Tom Loftin, 1854-1911. (Box 31)
- Johnston, Samuel, 1733-1816. (Box 31)
- Jones, Jenkin Lloyd, 1843-1918. (Box 31)
- Jones, John Paul, 1747-1792. (Box 31)
- Jones, Leroi, 1934 - (Box 31)
- Jones, Mary (Harris) "Mother", 1830-1930. (Box 31)
- Jones, Samuel Milton, 1846-1904. (Box 31)
- Jones, Wesley Livsey, 1863-1932. (Box 31)
- Jones, William, 1760-1831. (Box 31)
- Jones, Willie, 1741?-1801 (Box 31)
- Joseph, Nez Percés, chief, 1840-1904. (Box 31)
- Jubilee singers. (Box 31)
- Kalakaua, David, king of Hawaii, 1836-1891. (Box 31)
- Kane, Elisha Kent, 1820-1857. (Box 31)
- Kansas City, Missouri. (Box 31)
- Kansas., [2 folders.] (Box 31)
- Keeler, Ralph Olmstead, 1840-1873. (Box 31)
- Keen, William Williams, 1837-1932. (Box 31)
- Kefauver, Estes, 1903-1963. (Box 42)
- Keller, Helen Adams, 1880 - (Box 42)
- Kelley, Florence, 1859-1932. (Box 42)
- Kelly, Howard Atwood, 1848-1943. (Box 42)
- Kemble, Edward Windsor, 1861-1933. (Box 42)
- Kennan, George, 1845-1924. (Box 42)
- Kennedy, Jacqueline Lee (Bouvier), 1929 - (Box 32)
- Kennedy, John F. (Box Unknown container 231 for instance of Kennedy, John F.)
- Kennedy, John Pendleton, 1795-1870. (Box 32)
- Kent, James, 1763-1847. (Box 32)
- Kentucky. (Box 32)
- Kenyon, William Squire, 1869-1933. (Box 32)
- Kern, John Worth, 1849-1917. (Box 32)
- Kerouac, John, 1922-1969. (Box 32)
- Key, Francis Scott, 1779-1843. (Box 32)
- Kilpatrick, Hugh Judson, 1836-1881. (Box 32)
- King Ranch, Texas. (Box 32)
- King, Martin Luther, 1929-1968., [10 folders.] (Box 85)
- King, Martin Luther, 1929-1968., [2 folders.] (Box 122)
- Kitt Peak, Arizona. (Box 32)
- Knopf, Alfred A., 1892 - (Box 32)
- Knox, Philander Chase, 1853-1921. (Box 32)
- Koda gems. (Box 32)
- Kosinski, Jerzy N., 1933 - (Box 32)
- Kreymborg, Alfred, 1883 - (Box 32)
- Krutch, Joseph Wood, 1893-1970. (Box 32)
- Kunz, George Frederick, 1856-1932. (Box 32)
- La Farge, Oliver, 1901-1963. (Box 32)
- La Guardia, Fiorello Henry, 1882-1947. (Box 42)
- Labor and laboring classes-U.S. (Box 32)
- Ladd, George Trumball, 1842-1921. (Box 32)
- LaFollette, Robert Marion, 1855 -1925. (Box 42)
- Lamberton, William Alexander, 1848 -1910. (Box 42)
- Land titles-Louisiana. (Box 42)
- Lane, Franklin Knight, 1864-1921. (Box 42)
- Lane, Harry, 1855-1917. (Box 42)
- Langer, William, 1866 - (Box 42)
- Langley, John Wesley, d. 1932. (Box 33)
- Lansing, Robert, 1864-1928. (Box 33)
- Lardner, Ring Wilmer, 1885-1933. (Box 33)
- Las Aminas County, Colorado. (Box 33)
- Las Vegas, Nevada. (Box 33)
- Las Vegas, Nevada., [4 folders.] (Box 125)
- Lathrop, George Parsons, 1851-1898. (Box 33)
- Lathrop, Rose Hawthorne, 1851-1926. (Box 33)
- Latrobe, John Hazlehurst Boneval, 1803-1891. (Box 33)
- Lattimore, Deborah Nourse. (Box 33)
- Laughlin, James, 1914 - (Box 33)
- Laughlin, John Clarence. (Box 33)
- Laurens, Henry, 1724-1792. (Box 33)
- Laurens, John, 1754-1782. (Box 33)
- Law, Alice, d. 1896. (Box 33)
- Lawrence, Abbott, 1792-1855. (Box 33)
- Lawrence, T.B.? (Box 33)
- Lawson, Roberta (Campbell), d. 1940. (Box 33)
- Lea, Henry Charles, 1825-1909. (Box 33)
- Lea, Luke, 1879-1945. (Box 33)
- League of Women Voters of the United States. (Box 33)
- Lee, George Washington Custis, 1832-1913. (Box 33)
- Lee, Gerald Stanley, 1862-1944. (Box 33)
- Lee, Henry, 1756-1818. (Box 33)
- Lee, Robert Edward, 1807-1870. (Box 33)
- Leidy, Joseph, 1823-1891. (Box 33)
- Leland, Charles Godfrey, 1824 -1903. (Box 33)
- Lewis and Clark Expedition. (Box 33)
- Lewis Carroll Society of North America. (Box 33)
- Lewis, James Hamilton, 1863-1939. (Box 33)
- Lewis, James, 1826-1896. (Box 33)
- Lewis, John Llewellyn, 1880 - (Box 33)
- Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951. (Box 33)
- Liberty Party. Pittsburgh, 1844. (Box 121)
- Libraries. (Box 42)
- Light-ships. (Box 42)
- Lincoln homestead. (Box Unknown container 232 for instance of Lincoln homestead.)
- Lincoln, Abraham., [2 folders.] (Box 43)
- Lincoln, Benjamin, 1733-1810. (Box 42)
- Lincoln, Robert Todd, 1843-1926. (Box 42)
- Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, 1902-1974. (Box 42)
- Lindsay, Nicholas Vachel, 1879-1931. (Box 43)
- Lindsey, Benjamin Barr, 1869-1943., [2 folders.] (Box 43)
- Linn, Thomas B. (Box 34)
- Lippett, Henry Frederick, 1856-1933. (Box 34)
- Lippmann, Walter, 1889 - (Box 34)
- Livermore, Mary Ashton Rice, 1820-1905. (Box 34)
- Livingston, Edward, 1764-1836. (Box 34)
- Livingston, Robert R., 1746-1813. (Box 34)
- Llano Del Rio, Louisiana. (Box 34)
- Lloyd, Henry Demarest, 1847-1903. (Box 34)
- Lloyd, John Uri, 1849-1936. (Box 34)
- Lockwood, Belva Ann Bennett, 1830-1917. (Box 34)
- Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1850-1924. (Box 34)
- Loeb, William, 1866-1937. (Box 34)
- Logan, John Alexander, 1826-1886. (Box 34)
- Lohse, Henry. (Box 34)
- Long, Huey Pierce, 1893-1935. (Box 34)
- Long, John Davis, 1838 -1915. (Box 34)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, 1807-1882. (Box 34)
- Longfellow, Samuel, 1819-1892. (Box 34)
- Los Alamos, NM (Box 34)
- Los Angeles, Calif.-Harbor. (Box 121)
- Lossing, Benson John, 1813-1891. (Box 34)
- Louisiana. (Box 34)
- Lovejoy, Elijah Parish, 1802-1837. (Box 34)
- Lovett, Robert Morse, 1870 - (Box 34)
- Lowell, Amy, 1874-1925. (Box 34)
- Lowell, James Russell, 1819-1891. (Box 34)
- Lowell, Percival, 1855-1916. (Box 34)
- Lowenfels, Walter, 1897 - (Box 34)
- Loyalty oaths. (Box 34)
- Luhan, Mabel (Ganson) Dodge, 1879-1962. (Box 34)
- Lyle, Eugene Percy, 1873 - (Box 35)
- Lynes, George Platt. (Box 35)
- Lyon, Nathaniel, 1818-1861. (Box 35)
- MacArthur, Douglas, 1880-1964. (Box 35)
- MacDonald, Dwight, 1906-1982. (Box 35)
- MacDonough, Thomas, 1783-1825. (Box 35)
- MacDowell, Edward Alexander, 1861-1908. (Box 35)
- Machen, Augustus W. (Box 35)
- MacKay, Clarence Hungerford, 1879-1938. (Box 35)
- MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982. (Box 35)
- Madison, Dorothy (Payne) Todd, 1768-1849. (Box 35)
- Maine. (Box Unknown container 233 for instance of Maine.)
  1. Maine-views.
- Maine. (Box 43)
- Mann, Horance, 1796-1859. (Box 43)
- Manners and customs. (Box 43)
- Manning, William Thomas, bp., 1866 - (Box 43)
- Mantle, Lee, 1851-1934. (Box 43)
- Marcy, William Learned, 1786-1857. (Box 43)
- Marias Pass, Montana. (Box 43)
- Marion, Francis, 1732-1795. (Box 36)
- Marsh, Othniel Charles, 1831-1899. (Box 36)
- Marshall, James Wilson, 1812-1885. (Box 36)
- Marshall, John, 1755-1835. (Box 36)
- Marshall, John, 1835-1882. (Box 36)
- Marshall, Thomas Riley, 1854-1925. (Box 36)
- Martin, Alexander, 1740-1807. (Box 36)
- Martine, James Edgar, 1850-1925. (Box 36)
- Marvin, Richard Pratt, 1803-1892. (Box 36)
- Maryland. (Box 36)
- Mason, John Young, 1799-1859. (Box 36)
- Mason, Lowell, 1792-1872. (Box 36)
- Mason, William E., 1850-1921. (Box 36)
- Massachusetts. (Box 36)
- Mather, Stephen Tyng, 1867-1930. (Box 36)
- Matthews, Stanley, 1824-1889. (Box 36)
- Maxwell, George Hebard, 1860-1946. (Box 36)
- May, Samuel Joseph, 1797-1871. (Box 36)
- Mayflower II. (Box 36)
- Mayo, Charles Horace, 1869-1939. (Box 36)
- Mayo, William James, 1861-1939. (Box 36)
- McAdoo, William Gibbs, 1863-1941. (Box 35)
- McCarthy, Eugene J., 1916 - (Box 35)
- McCarthy, Mary Therese, 1912 - (Box 35)
- McClellan, George Brinton, 1826-1885. (Box 35)
- McClung, David W., 1831 - (Box 35)
- McClure, Samuel Sidney, 1857-1949. (Box 35)
- McCosh, James, 1811-1894. (Box 35)
- McCulloch, Hugh, 1808 - (Box 35)
- McCutcheon, George Barr, 1866-1928. (Box 35)
- McGovern, George, 1922 - (Box 35)
- McKenzie, Robert Tait, 1867-1938. (Box 35)
- McKinley, William. (Box 35)
- McLane, Louis, 1786-1857. (Box 35)
- McMaster, John Bach, 1852-1932. (Box 35)
- Mead, Edwin Doak, 1849-1937. (Box 36)
- Meade, George Gordon, 1815-1872. (Box 36)
- Meade, Henrietta. (Box 36)
- Medford, Oregon. (Box 36)
- Medicines, patent, proprietary, etc. (Box 36)
- Medicines, patent, proprietary, etc. (Box 121)
- Medill, Joseph, 1823-1899. (Box 36)
- Melville, Herman, 1819-1891. (Box 44)
- Mencken, Henry Louis, 1880 - (Box 44)
- Mesa Verde National Park (Box 44)
- Messmer, Sebastian Gebhard, Bp., 1847-1930. (Box 44)
- Mexicans in the U.S. (Box 37)
- Meyer, George von Lengerke, 1858-1918. (Box 37)
- Meyercord, George Rudolph, 1875 - (Box 37)
- Michals, Duane Steven, 1932 - (Box 37)
- Michigan. (Box 37)
- Middle Borden Bulletin. Mitchell, S.D. (Box 37)
- Miles, Nelson Appleton, 1839-1925. (Box 37)
- Miller, Mrs. Harriet (Mann), 1831-1918. (Box 37)
- Milwaukee. (Box 37)
- Mines and mineral resources-Alaska. (Box 37)
- Mines and mineral resources-Arizona. (Box 37)
- Mines and mineral resources-Nevada. (Box 37)
- Minnesota. Univesity. Library. The Kerlan Collection. (Box 37)
- Missions-Arizona. (Box 37)
- Missions-New Mexico. (Box 37)
- Missions-Texas. (Box 44)
- Mississippi. (Box 44)
- Missouri. (Box 44)
- Mitchell, Donald Grant, 1822-1908. (Box 44)
- Mitchell, John, 1870-1919. (Box 44)
- Mitchell, Silas Weir, 1829-1914. (Box 38)
- Monnett, Frank S. (Box 38)
- Monroe, Harriet, 1860-1936. (Box 38)
- Montana., [2 folders.] (Box 38)
- Montana., [5 folders.] (Box 120)
- Montezuma Society. (Box 38)
- Moody, Dwight Lyman, 1837-1899. (Box 38)
- Moore, John Howard, 1862-1916. (Box 38)
- Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972., [2 folders.] (Box 38)
- Moore, Willis Luther, 1856-1927. (Box 38)
- Moran, Thomas, 1836-1926. (Box 38)
- Morey, Samuel, 1762-1843. (Box 38)
- Morgan, Barbara Brooks, 1900 - (Box 38)
- Morgan, Matthew Somerville, 1839-1890. (Box 38)
- Morley, Christopher Darlington, 1890 - (Box 38)
- Mormons and Mormonism., [5 folders.] (Box 86)
- Morris, Robert, 1734-1806. (Box 44)
- Morris, Robert, 1818-1888. (Box 44)
- Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1791-1872. (Box 44)
- Morton, Joy (Box 44)
- Morton, Samuel George, 1799-1851. (Box 44)
- Moseley, Edward Augustus, 1846-1911. (Box 44)
- Moser, Barry, 1940 - (Box 44)
- Mother's Day. (Box 44)
- Mott, Lucretia (Coffin), 1793-1880. (Box 44)
- Moulton, Ellen Louise (Chandler), 1835-1908. (Box 44)
- Moultrie, William, 1730-1805. (Box 44)
- Mount Holyoke College. South Hadley, Mass., [8 folders.] (Box 124)
- Mount Hood, Oregon. (Box Unknown container 234 for instance of Mount Hood, Oregon.)
- Mount Ranier National Park. (Box 44)
- Mount Zion National Park, Utah. (Box Unknown container 235 for instance of Mount Zion National Park, Utah.)
- Mountaineering-bibliography-catalogues. (Box 117)
- Moving-picture cameras. (Box 44)
- Murfreesboro, Battle of, 1862-1863. (Box Unknown container 236 for instance of Murfreesboro, Battle of, 1862-1863.)
- Murphy, John Benjamin, 1857-1916. (Box 39)
- Murphy, Nathan Oakes, 1849-1908. (Box 39)
- Music. (Box 39)
- Muskogee, Oklahoma. (Box 39)
- Mystery Reader's Newsletter (The). Melrose, Mass. (Box 44)
- Nash, Abner, ca. 1740-1798. (Box 39)
- Nast, Thomas, 1840-1902. (Box 39)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People. (Box 39)
- National Citizens Political Action Committee. (Box 39)
- National Council on Aging. (Box 39)
- National Cowboy Hall of Fame. Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. (Box 117)
- National defense-U.S. (Box 117)
- National Gallery fo Art. Washington, D.C. (Box 117)
- National Immigration Convention. (Box 39)
- National Organization of Women. (Box 39)
- National parks and reserves-U.S., [2 folders.] (Box 39)
- National Trust for Historic Preservation in the United States., [5 folders.] (Box 40)
- National Wildlife Federation. (Box 45)
- Nature Conservancy (The). Arlington, Virginia. (Box 45)
- Navaho Indians. (Box 45)
- Neal, Joseph Clay, 1807-1847. (Box 45)
- Nebraska. (Box 45)
- Negro authors. (Box 45)
- Negro literature-bibliography-catalogs. (Box 45)
- Negroes. (Box 44)
- Neill, Charles Patrick, 1865-1942. (Box 44)
- Nelson, Knuts, 1843-1923. (Box 45)
- Nelson, Nason Olsen, 1844-1922. (Box 45)
- Nevada. (Box 46)
- Nevin, Ethelbert Woodbridge, 1862-1901. (Box 46)
- New Hampshire. (Box 46)
- New Jersey. (Box 46)
- New Mexico., [2 folders.] (Box 46)
- New Orleans, Louisiana., [2 folders.] (Box 107)
- New York (City)., [5 folders.] (Box 47)
- New York (State)., [Box 127 contains 2 folders.] (Box 127, Box 47)
- New York State Historical Society. (Box 47)
- Newberry, John Strong, 1822-1892. (Box 107)
- Newell, Frederick Haynes, 1862-1932. (Box 107)
- Newlands, Francis Griffith, 1848-1917. (Box 107)
- Newman, John Philip, 1826 - (Box 107)
- Newton, Alfred Edward, 1863-1940. (Box 107)
- Newton, Richard Heber, 1840-1914. (Box 107)
- Niagara Falls. (Box 107)
- Night Kitchen (The). New York, New York. (Box 117)
- Norris, George William, 1861-1944. (Box 107)
- North Carolina. (Box 107)
- North Dakota. (Box 107)
- Noyes, Edward Follensbee, 1832-1890. (Box 107)
- Nutting, Wallace, 1861-1941. (Box 108)
- Nye, Edgar Wilson, 1850-1896. (Box 48)
- Nye, Gerald Prentice, 1892 - (Box 48)
- O'Connor, Michael Patrick, 1831-1881. (Box 48)
- O'Dea, Edward John, 1856-1932. (Box 48)
- Odlum, Hortense McQuarrie, 1892-1970. (Box 48)
- O'Donnell, Jessie Fremont, 1860-1897. (Box 48)
- Ogden, Aaron, 1756-1839. (Box 47)
- Ohio. (Box 48)
- Oklahoma. (Box 48)
- Olcott, Chauncey, 1860-1932. (Box 48)
- Olson, Charles, 1910 - (Box 48)
- Olympics (25th: 1992 Barcelona, Spain). (Box 48)
- O'Neal, Edward Asbury, 1875-1958. (Box 48)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone, 1888-1953. (Box 48)
- Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1904 - (Box 48)
- Oregon. (Box 108)
- Osgood, Frances Sargent (Locke), 1811-1850. (Box 48)
- Ossoli, Sara Margaret (Fuller), 1810-1850. (Box 48)
- Oswald, Felix leopold, 1845-1906. (Box 48)
- Otero, Miguel Antonio, 1859-1944. (Box 48)
- Overman, Lee Slater, 1854-1930. (Box 49)
- Owen, Richard, 1810-1890. (Box 49)
- Owen, Robert Latham, 1856-1947. (Box 49)
- Oxnam, Garfield Bromley, 1891 - (Box 49)
- Oxner, Fred P. (Box 49)
- Ozark Mountains. (Box 49)
- Pacific Northwest Library Association. (Box 49)
- Paine, George M. (Box 49)
- Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809. (Box 49)
- Palm Beach, Florida. (Box 49)
- Palmer, Ray, 1808-1887. (Box 49)
- Parker, Alton Brooks, 1852-1926. (Box 49)
- Parker, Theodore, 1810-1860. (Box 49)
- Parkhurst, Charles Henry, 1842-1933. (Box 49)
- Parkman, Francis, 1823-1893. (Box 49)
- Parsons, Reginald Hascall, 1873 - (Box 49)
- Parton, James, 1822-1891. (Box 49)
- Patent medicines. SEE: Medicines, patent, proprietary, etc. (Box Unknown container 237 for instance of Patent medicines. SEE: Medicines, patent, proprietary, etc.)
- Patten, Francis Landey, 1843 - (Box 49)
- Paul, Elliot Harold, 1891-1958. (Box 49)
- Peabody, George, 1795-1869. (Box 49)
- Peace-societies. (Box 49)
- Peace Corps. Washington, D.C. (Box 117)
- Pegler, James Westbrook, 1894-1969. (Box 49)
- Pendleton, George Hunt, 1825-1889. (Box 49)
- Penn, William, 1644-1718. (Box 49)
- Penniman, Josiah Harmar, 1868-1941. (Box 49)
- Pennsylvania. (Box 49)
- Penrose, Boies, 1860-1921. (Box 108)
- Pepper, William, 1843-1898. (Box 108)
- Perelman, Sidney Joseph, 1904 - (Box 108)
- Periodicals, publishing of., [4 folders.] (Box 50)
- Periodicals, publishing of., [4 folders.] (Box 51)
- Perkins, Frances, 1882 - (Box 52)
- Perkins, Thomas Handasyd, 1764-1854. (Box 52)
- Perry, Nora, 1831-1896. (Box 52)
- Perry, Oliver Hazzard, 1785-1819. (Box 52)
- Pershing, John Joseph, 1860 - (Box 52)
- Petrified Forest National Monument, Arizona. (Box 52)
- Petroleum industry and trade-U.S. (Box 52)
- Pettigrew, Richard Franklin, 1848-1926. (Box 52)
- Peyote. (Box 108)
- Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943. (Box 108)
- Phi Beta Kappa. Virginia Alpha, William and Mary College. (Box 108)
- Philadelphia. (Box 108)
- Philipp, Emanuel Lorenz, 1861-1925. (Box 108)
- Philips, Shine. (Box 108)
- Phillips, Wendell, 1811-1884. (Box 108)
- Phoenix, Arizona. (Box 108)
- Photography-bibliography-catalogs, booksellers'., [4 folders.] (Box 52)
- Photography-bibliography-catalogs, publishers'., [5 folders.] (Box 53)
- Photography-exhibitions-catalogs., [5 folders.] (Box 88)
- Photography-exhibitions-catalogs., [5 folders.] (Box 88)
- Photography-exhibitions., [4 folders.] (Box 54)
- Photography-preservation. (Box 90)
- Photography-U.S., [5 folders.] (Box 89)
- Photography-U.S., [4 folders.] (Box 90)
- Piatt, Donn, 1819-1891. (Box 109)
- Piatt, John James, 1835-1917. (Box 109)
- Pickering, Timothy, 1745-1829. (Box 109)
- Pierpont, John, 1785-1866. (Box 109)
- Pike, Albert, 1809-1891. (Box 109)
- Pike, Zebulon Montgomery, 1779-1813. (Box 109)
- Pike's Peak, Colorado. (Box 109)
- Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946. (Box 109)
- Pinchot, James Wallace, 1831-1908. (Box 109)
- Pinckney, Charles Cotesworth, 1748-1825. (Box 109)
- Pingree, Hazan Stuart, 1840 -1901. (Box 55)
- Pitman, Benn, 1822-1910. (Box 55)
- Pittman, Key, 1872-1940. (Box 55)
- Pittsburgh. (Box 55)
- Plath, Sylvia, 1832-1963. (Box 55)
- Pocahontus, d. 1617. (Box 55)
- Poe, Edgar Allan, 1809-1849. (Box 55)
- Poindexter, Miles, 1868-1946. (Box 55)
- Poinsett, Joel Roberts, 1779-1851. (Box 55)